John Alden Mason Papers 1904-1967 Mss.B.M384
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1926-1967; 20 linear feet
  - Browne, Herbert Janvrin (Box 10)
  - Brugge, David M. (Box 10)
    - Caso, Alfonso (Box 10)
    - Fejos, Paul (Box 10)
  - Brundage, Burr C (Box 10)
  - Brunhouse, Robert L (Box 10)
  - Bryan, Kirk (Box 10)
  - Bryant, Dick (Box 10)
  - Brysch, O. P (Box 10)
  - Buck, Bob (Box 11)
  - Buck, Peter H (Box 11)
  - Bucks County Historical Society (Box 11)
  - Buffalo, N.Y. Museum of Science (Box 11)
    - Fish, Charles J (Box 11)
    - Hamlin, Chauncey J (Box 11)
  - Bunker, Frank F (Box 11)
  - Bunzel Ruth L (Box 11)
  - Buob, Coralie (Box 11)
  - Burch, William L (Box 11)
  - Burke, Theresa M., Employment Agency (Box 11)
  - Burkitt, Robert (Box 11)
  - Burkitt, Robert, Estate (Box 11)
  - Burnett, E. Ken (Box 11)
  - Burnette, F. O (Box 11)
  - Burpee, W. Atlee, Co (Box 11)
  - Burr, Pamela (Box 11)
  - Burry, Edmund (Box 11)
  - Burton, Horace H (Box 11)
  - Burvant, R. D (Box 11)
  - Busbey, Ralph C (Box 11)
  - Bushnell, G. H. S (Box 11)
  - Butler, George T (Box 11)
  - Butler, Mary (Box 11)
  - Butler, Thomas S (Box 11)
  - Bye, Arthur Edwin (Box 11)
  - Byers, Douglas S (Box 11)
    - Longyear, John M III (Box 11)
    - Scott, Donald (Box 11)
  - Cáceres Freyre, Julián B (Box 11)
  - Córdoba, Joaquín Fernández de (Box 11)
  - Cabana, A. E (Box 11)
  - Cabot, Godfrey L., Inc (Box 11)
  - Cabot, Thomas D (Box 11)
  - Cadwalader, Charles. M. B (Box 11)
  - Cadzow, Donald A (Box 11)
  - Cahall, Lawrence M., III (Box 11)
  - Cahill, Holger (Box 11)
  - Cain, Lottie (Box 11)
  - Cakchiquel, Annals of the...publication (Box 11)
  - Cala Ramos, Jose D (Box 11)
  - Calderón, Ramon (Box 11)
  - Caldwell, Harmon (Box 11)
  - Caldwell. J.E. Caldwell Co (Box 11)
  - Cale, Edgar B (Box 11)
  - Calkin, Carleton I (Box 11)
  - Call, Mrs. O. F (Box 11)
  - Cammann, Schuyler (Box 11)
  - Campbell, T. N (Box 11)
    See also Donald Scott file
  - Campbell, William Martin (Box 11)
  - Canada. The Imperial Airways of Canada. Dickens, C.H (Box 11)
  - Canadian Airways Ltd (Box 11)
    - Dickins, C H (Box 11)
  - Canary, Clarence A (Box 11)
  - Canel, L (Box 11)
  - Canevares, B. G (Box 11)
  - Canner, J S & Co (Box 11)
    - Lebowitz, Marshall (Box 11)
  - Caplan, Allan (Box 11)
  - Cardenas-Garcia, Cesar (Box 11)
  - Carl, Walter (Box 11)
  - Carlock, E. A (Box 11)
  - Carnegie Corporation (Box 11)
  - Carnegie Institution of Washington (Box 11)
  - Carnegie Museum, Pittsburgh (Box 11)
    - Avinoff, A (Box 11)
    - Holland, W J (Box 11)
    - Steward, Douglas (Box 11)
  - Carneiro, Robert (Box 11)
  - Carpenter, Edmund S (Box 11)
  - Carr, J. E (Box 11)
  - Carr, James H (Box 11)
  - Carrasco, Pedro (Box 11)
  - Carrasco, Pizana, Pedro (Box 11)
  - Carrion Cachot, Rebecca (Box 11)
  - Carsten, Ruth (Box 11)
  - Carter, George F (Box 11)
  - Carter, Ray E (Box 11)
  - Casanova, Richard L (Box 11)
  - Case, F. L (Box 11)
  - Caso, Alfonso (Box 11)
  - Cassidy, Francis E (Box 11)
  - Casson, Stanley (Box 11)
  - Castillo Hijo, Nicanor (Box 11)
  - Castillo, Antonio (Box 11)
  - Castro Leal, Antonio (Box 11)
  - Castro, Gorge Fernández de (Box 11)
  - Catlin, George, notebook, report on (Box 11)
  - Cattell, J. McKean (Box 11)
  - Cattell, Jaques (Box 11)
  - Cavallo, Adolph S (Box 11)
    - Witte, Emily H (Box 11)
  - Cerezo, Hugo (Box 11)
  - Cerna, Carlos Giron (Box 11)
  - Cervenka, Ladislaus F (Box 11)
  - Chadwick, James M (Box 12)
  - Chambers, Mrs. Elizabeth Long (Box 12)
  - Chancellor, J W (Box 12)
  - Chandler, Charles Lyon (Box 12)
    - Jayne, Horace H F (Box 12)
  - Chaninal, Elizabeth (Box 12)
  - Chapin, Pat (Box 12)
  - Chapple, Charles C (Box 12)
  - Charles, Victor A (Box 12)
  - Charleston Museum (Box 12)
  - Chartrand, Francine (Box 12)
    - Tolstoy, Paul (Box 12)
  - Chase, Gilbert (Box 12)
  - Chelf, Carl (Box 12)
  - Cheyenne: see Northern Chetenne Tribe (Box 12)
  - Chicago Natural History Museum (Box 12)
    - Gregg, Clifford C (Box 12)
  - Chisholm, James (Box 12)
    - Anderson, W H (Box 12)
    - Fisher, Gerhard (Box 12)
    - Hart, Thomas (Box 12)
  - Christensen, Bodil (Box 12)
    - Calle, Chita de la (Box 12)
    - Sociedad Mexicana de Antropologia (Box 12)
  - Christensen, R (Box 12)
  - Christensen, Robert (Box 12)
  - Christensen, Ross T (Box 12)
  - Christian, Floyd T (Box 12)
  - Chrone, R E (Box 12)
  - Chrystie, Margaret H (Box 12)
  - Church, Franklin H (Box 12)
  - Cinquemani, Mrs. Dorothy Kyte (Box 12)
  - Clément, André (Box 12)
  - Clark, Herbert C (Box 12)
  - Clark, John W (Box 12)
  - Clark (Box 12)
  - Clarke, A. J (Box 12)
  - Clausen, Carl (Box 12)
  - Clave, Harry M (Box 12)
  - Clements, Forrest E (Box 12)
  - Clemons, D. R (Box 12)
  - Cleveland Museum of Art (Box 12)
  - Clive-Smith, H (Box 12)
  - Clothier, William J II (Box 12)
  - Coates, James R (Box 12)
  - Cobb, Mrs. Edna (Box 12)
  - Cobb, W. Montague (Box 12)
  - Cochrane, James (Box 12)
  - Cocle catalogue (Box 12)
  - Coffey, Katherine (Box 12)
  - Cofield, J W (Box 12)
  - Cogswell, George (Box 12)
  - Colby, Cynthia (Box 12)
  - Cole, Fay-Cooper (Box 12)
  - Coleman, Laurence Vail (Box 12)
  - Coles, Stricker (Box 12)
  - Colgrave, Bertram (Box 12)
  - Collester, Clinton H (Box 12)
  - Collier, Donald (Box 12)
  - Collier, F. P. & Son, Corp (Box 12)
    - Beardsley, W W (Box 12)
  - Collier, John (Box 12)
    - Bennett, Wendell (Box 12)
  - Collier, Nina P (Box 12)
  - Collings, G R (Box 12)
  - Collins, G. N (Box 12)
  - Collins, Henry B., Jr (Box 12)
  - Colman, Wilton H (Box 12)
  - Colt, Martha C (Box 12)
  - Colton, Harold S (Box 12)
  - Columbia University Press (Box 12)
    - Sickels, Dorothy (Box 12)
  - Comas, Juan (Box 12)
    - Gamio, Manuel (Box 12)
  - Combes, Horace M (Box 12)
  - Compton, Carl B (Box 12)
  - Conde, José Alvarez (Box 12)
  - Conklin, E G (Box 12)
  - Considine, Constance M (Box 12)
  - Conte, Miguel A (Box 12)
  - Conyes, A. S (Box 12)
  - Cook de Leonard, Carmen (Box 12)
  - Cook, Harold J (Box 12)
  - Cook, Robert C., Co (Box 12)
  - Cooks, Anne M (Box 12)
  - Cooper, George L (Box 12)
  - Cooper, John W (Box 12)
    - Flannery, Regina (Box 12)
  - Corbett, John M (Box 12)
  - Cordon, Emilio (Box 12)
  - Cormack, Maribelle (Box 12)
  - Corning, John B. & Julia H (Box 12)
  - Corning, John B (Box 12)
  - Corning, John (Box 12)
  - Corning, Leavitt, Jr (Box 12)
  - Corrin, K. M (Box 12)
  - Corson, Edward F (Box 12)
  - Cosgrove, C. B (Box 12)
  - Coston, Cecil P (Box 12)
  - Cotter, John L (Box 12)
  - Coulter, John S (Box 12)
  - Cowan, J. M (Box 12)
  - Craighead, Jean (Box 12)
  - Cramer, Seward S (Box 12)
  - Cranbrook Institute of Science (Box 12)
    - Hatt, Robert T (Box 12)
  - Crane, Jacob L Jr (Box 12)
  - Crawford, Kenneth J (Box 12)
  - Crawford, M. D. C (Box 12)
  - Crawford, W. Rex (Box 12)
  - Creaghead, Elizabeth (Box 12)
  - Creer, Doris (Box 12)
  - Crequi Montfort, Marquis de (Box 12)
    - Société des Américanistes de Paris (Box 12)
    - Rivet, Paul (Box 12)
  - Cressman, Luther S (Box 12)
  - Cresson, Francis M., Jr (Box 12)
    - Swift, David E (Box 12)
  - Crimmins, M. L (Box 12)
  - Crosby, H. Lamar (Box 13)
  - Crosley. Icyball Division (Box 13)
  - Cross, Dorothy (Box 13)
  - Cross, Dorothy (Box 13)
    - Geisman, Jane (Box 13)
  - Crozier, Archibald (Box 13)
  - Cruxent, José (Box 13)
  - Cubbage, William O (Box 13)
  - Cubley, Herbert R (Box 13)
  - Cumming, Burton (Box 13)
  - Cummings, Byron (Box 13)
  - Cummings, H. M (Box 13)
  - Cummings, John (Box 13)
  - Cunningham, Allan (Box 13)
  - Cunningham, Mrs. J E B (Box 13)
  - Curbishley, David L (Box 13)
  - Curry, Douglas (Box 13)
  - Curry, William (Box 13)
  - Curtis, Alonzo H (Box 13)
  - Curtis, Karl P (Box 13)
  - Curtis, Karl (Box 13)
  - Curtis, S. H (Box 13)
  - Cutillo, Frank D (Box 13)
  - Cutter, Victor M (Box 13)
  - Dávalos Hurtado, Eusebio (Box 13)
  - Dörffel, Felix (Box 13)
  - Dahl, Alvin (Box 13)
  - Dahlman, Sven (Box 13)
  - Daigh, Ralph (Box 13)
  - Daland, Judson (Box 13)
  - Dale, John T (Box 13)
  - Dalrymple, George H (Box 13)
  - Daly, Lloyd W (Box 13)
  - Dam, Mrs. Cornelia (Box 13)
  - Dana, Alan Standish (Box 13)
  - Danson, Edward B (Box 13)
    - Colton, Harold S (Box 13)
    - Northern Arizona Society of Science & Art, Inc (Box 13)
  - Danzel, Th W (Box 13)
  - Darr, H. C (Box 13)
  - Darte, Katherine D (Box 13)
  - Daugherty, Mrs. Katherine (Box 13)
  - Dauterman, Carl C (Box 13)
    - Wardle, Harriet Newell (Box 13)
  - Davalos Hurtado, Eusebio (Box 13)
    - Sociedad Mexicana de Antropologia (Box 13)
  - Davenport, Charles B (Box 13)
  - David, Joseph A (Box 13)
  - Davidson, D. S (Box 13)
  - Davidson, Julius (Box 13)
  - Davis, Arthur Kyle, Jr (Box 13)
  - Davis, Bernard (Box 13)
  - Davis, Edward H (Box 13)
  - Davis, Elizabeth M (Box 13)
  - Davis, Emily C (Box 13)
  - Davis, Joseph A (Box 13)
  - Davis, Roy Tasco (Box 13)
  - Davis, Uarda K (Box 13)
  - Davis, William T (Box 13)
  - Davison, Edwin H (Box 13)
  - Dawson, Leonard G (Box 13)
  - Day, H Summerfield (Box 13)
  - Day, Kenneth (Box 13)
  - De Laguna, Frederica (Box 13)
  - De Peso, Charles C (Box 13)
  - Deardorff, Minnie P (Box 13)
  - Debenedetti, Salvatore (Box 13)
  - Deevey, Edward S (Box 13)
  - Deisher, Henry K (Box 13)
  - DeLaguna, Frederica (Box 13)
  - Delany, Lyons F H (Box 13)
  - Delaware County Institute of Science (Box 13)
    - Streeper, Edward V (Box 13)
  - Dellinger, S C (Box 13)
  - Delores, Juan (Box 13)
  - Del Rio, Pablo Martinez (Box 13)
  - DeMendizabal, Miguel O (Box 13)
  - Denlinger, Elmer (Box 13)
  - Denny, Grace (Box 13)
  - Dentma, Fr (Box 13)
  - Derry, C H (Box 13)
  - DeTerra, Helmut (Box 13)
  - DeVelde, Elizabeth A (Box 13)
  - Dexter, Ralph W (Box 13)
  - Diamond, Stanley (Box 13)
    - Moore, Stanley (Box 13)
  - Diaz y de Ova, Clementine (Box 13)
  - Dibble, Charles E (Box 13)
  - Dickey, Janet W (Box 13)
  - Dickey, Parke A (Box 13)
  - Dictionary of American History (Box 13)
  - Didier,G M (Box 13)
  - Dieseldorff, Erwin P (Box 13)
    - Jayne, Horace H F (Box 13)
    - Satterthwaite, Linton, Jr (Box 13)
  - Dietz, Albert G. H (Box 13)
  - Dietz, Manuel J (Box 13)
  - Diez-Canedo, Joaquin (Box 13)
  - Dilks, Mrs (Box 13)
  - Dillaway, Theodore M (Box 13)
  - Dimmick, Edgar L (Box 13)
  - Dimock, Frances E (Box 13)
  - Divis, Frank G (Box 13)
  - Dixon, E. R (Box 13)
  - Dixon, Joseph Kossuth (Box 13)
  - Dixon, Keith A (Box 13)
  - Dockstader, Frederick J (Box 13)
    - Museum of the American Indian, Heye Foundation (Box 13)
  - Dodge, Ernest S (Box 13)
  - Dodge, John V (Box 13)
  - Doering, H V (Box 13)
    - Museums Für Völkerkunde, München (Box 13)
  - Dohan, Mrs. Joseph M (Box 13)
  - Doig, Federico Kauffmann (Box 13)
  - Domincovich, Harry (Box 13)
  - Dominguez, J. and A (Box 13)
  - Dominiguez, Miguel (Box 13)
    - Valdés, José Ramón (Box 13)
  - Donaldson, Dudley M (Box 13)
  - Donaldson, Henry H (Box 13)
  - Donovan, Judy (Box 13)
  - Dorn, David R (Box 14)
  - Dorrance, Frances (Box 14)
  - Dougherty, Edward (Box 14)
  - Dougherty, R. P (Box 14)
  - Douglas, Frederic H (Box 14)
  - Downes, Randolph C (Box 14)
  - Downey, Glanville (Box 14)
    - American Journal of Archeology (Box 14)
  - Downing, Todd (Box 14)
  - Drake, Robert J (Box 14)
  - Drake, William C (Box 14)
  - Draper, John W (Box 14)
  - Drey, Elizabeth M (Box 14)
  - Drucker, Philip (Box 14)
  - Duason, Jon (Box 14)
  - DuBarry, W (Box 14)
  - Dudley, Lavinia P (Box 14)
  - Duguid, D L (Box 14)
  - Dumont, Horace T., Jr (Box 14)
  - Dunn, E. R (Box 14)
  - Dunn, Montfort (Box 14)
  - Duque (Box 14)
  - Duque Gomez, Luis (Box 14)
  - Durland, W D (Box 14)
  - Dutcher, Willena B (Box 14)
  - Dutton, Bertha P (Box 14)
  - Duyvis, Mrs. Guda E G (Box 14)
  - Dwyre, Dudley G (Box 14)
  - Eachus, Mrs. Lola J (Box 14)
  - Easby, Dudley T & Mrs. Elizabeth Easby (Box 14)
  - Easby, Dudley T., Jr (Box 14)
  - East, Frank Russell (Box 14)
  - Eastern Shore Society of Baltimore City (Box 14)
  - Eastern States Archeological Federation., 1942-47, 1964 (Box 14)
    - Bird, Junius (Box 14)
    - Bogan, Samuel B (Box 14)
    - Boss, Edward C (Box 14)
    - Cadzow, Donald A (Box 14)
    - Cross, Dorothy (Box 14)
    - Crozier, Archibald (Box 14)
    - Davis, Harry T (Box 14)
    - Deardorff, M H (Box 14)
    - Fejos, Paul (Box 14)
    - Frank, Evelyn (Box 14)
    - Greywacz, Kathryn B (Box 14)
    - Hallett, Leaman F (Box 14)
    - Jerabek, Esther (Box 14)
    - Johnson, Frederick (Box 14)
    - Light, Richard (Box 14)
    - May, Philip S (Box 14)
    - Nelson, N C (Box 14)
    - Omwake, H Geiger (Box 14)
    - Pearsall, Leigh M (Box 14)
    - Rights, Douglas L (Box 14)
    - Ritchie, William A (Box 14)
    - Robbins, Maurice (Box 14)
    - Rouse, Irving (Box 14)
    - Streeter, Edwina W (Box 14)
    - Weslager, C A (Box 14)
  - Eastman Kodak Company (Box 15)
  - Echanove, Carlos A (Box 15)
  - Ecker, Lawrence (Box 15)
  - Eckert, Georg (Box 15)
  - Eckert, Samuel B (Box 15)
  - Eckert, Mrs. Samuel B (Box 15)
  - Eckhardt, George H (Box 15)
  - Edge, C. N (Box 15)
  - Edgerly, Mrs. Edna R (Box 15)
  - Edgerton, Franklin (Box 15)
    - Linguistic Institute of America (Box 15)
  - Edwards, Anne C. F (Box 15)
  - Edwards, Bill (Box 15)
  - Edwards, Mrs. J A (Box 15)
  - Edwards, Patrick (Box 15)
  - Egan-Dickeson Panorama - negotiations for sale, 1952-1958 (Box 15)
  - Egan-Dickeson Panorama, 1941 (Box 15)
  - Egbert, Jay Adrian (Box 15)
  - Eggan, Fred (Box 15)
  - Ehrich, Robert W (Box 15)
  - Eiman, John (Box 15)
  - Eiseley, Loren C (Box 15)
  - Eisemann, Edward (Box 15)
  - Eisenhart, Luther Phaler (Box 15)
  - Ekholm, Gordon F (Box 15)
  - Ekholm-Middle American Handbook (Box 15)
  - El Paso Times (Box 15)
    - Parrish, Joe (Box 15)
  - Elden, Emma J (Box 15)
  - Elder, Robert A., Jr (Box 15)
  - Eldridge, Maria (Box 15)
  - Elgar, C. S (Box 15)
  - Ellis, B. T (Box 15)
  - Ellis, H. Holmes (Box 15)
  - Elrod, Henry E (Box 15)
  - Elsnau, Mary (Box 15)
  - Elwood, William K (Box 15)
  - Emery, A. B (Box 15)
  - Emmons, G T (Box 15)
  - Emory, Kenneth P (Box 15)
  - Encyclopaedia Britannica (Box 15)
    - Blakely, Margaret G (Box 15)
    - Dodge, John V (Box 15)
    - Yust, Walter (Box 15)
  - Ende, Gerrit Vander (Box 15)
  - Enders, Robert K (Box 15)
  - Engerrand, George C (Box 15)
  - England, Stephen J (Box 15)
  - Epstein, Jeremiah F (Box 15)
  - Erie County Historical Soc (Box 15)
    - Reed, J E (Box 15)
  - Ervin, Spencer (Box 15)
  - Erwin, A. T (Box 15)
  - Erwin, John, Jr (Box 15)
  - Esberg, Alfred I (Box 15)
  - Escobar, Hector S (Box 15)
  - Escuela Nacional de Antropologia, Mexico (Box 15)
  - Eshelman, Ralph (Box 15)
  - Espana Libre (Box 15)
  - Espejo Nuñez, Julio (Box 15)
  - Espejo, Maria Antonieta (Box 15)
  - Espinosa, Aurelio M (Box 15)
  - Espinosa, J. Manuel (Box 15)
  - Esrey, Joseph L (Box 15)
  - Estrada, D A (Box 15)
  - Ethnic culture survey, Folkore, Folklife (Box 15)
  - Euler, Robert C (Box 15)
  - Euwema, Herman (Box 15)
  - Evans, Clifford, Jr (Box 15)
    - Kidder, Alfred, II (Box 15)
    - Palmatary, Helen C (Box 15)
    - Satterthwaite, Linton, Jr (Box 15)
    - Smithsonian Institution (Box 15)
  - Evans, S. C (Box 15)
  - Everett, Martha T (Box 15)
  - Ewers, John Canfield (Box 15)
  - Expéditions Polaires Françaises (Box 15)
  - Explorers' Club (Box 15)
    - Blossom, Frederick A (Box 15)
    - Granger, Walter (Box 15)
    - Herzog, L K (Box 15)
    - Kersting, Rudolph (Box 15)
    - Stefansson, Vilhjalmur (Box 15)
    - Talley, Harry S (Box 15)
    - Upham, Donald B (Box 15)
    - Winship, H H (Box 15)
    - Wright, Harry B (Box 15)
  - Eyman, Frances (Box 15)
  - Fairchild Aerial Surveys, Inc (Box 16)
  - Fairchild, Mildred (Box 16)
  - Falcey, Vivian (Box 16)
  - Falla, Salvador (Box 16)
  - Fanshave, D B (Box 16)
    - Voegelin, Carl F (Box 16)
  - Farabee, Mrs. C W (Box 16)
  - Farabee, Sylvia H (Box 16)
  - Farfan, J M B (Box 16)
  - Farr, Willoughby (Box 16)
  - Favour, Mrs. A H (Box 16)
  - Fay, George E (Box 16)
  - Fejos, Paul (Box 16)
    - Brugge, David M (Box 16)
    - Cross, Dorothy (Box 16)
    - Dell'Oro, Mary C (Box 16)
    - Greywacz, Kathryn B (Box 16)
    - Lebrija Celay, Antonio (Box 16)
    - Viking Fund (Box 16)
    - Wenner-Gren Foundation for Anthropological Research (Box 16)
  - Feller, Barbara (Box 16)
  - Fellows, Muriel H (Box 16)
  - Feltner, Flora A (Box 16)
  - Felton, Alice L (Box 16)
  - Fenenga, Franklin (Box 16)
  - Fenimore, Watson (Box 16)
  - Fenstermaker, G. B (Box 16)
  - Fenton, William N (Box 16)
  - Ferdon, Edwin N., Jr (Box 16)
  - Ferguson, Harold W (Box 16)
  - Ferguson, Thomas S (Box 16)
  - Fernald, Helen (Box 16)
  - Fernandez, Rodolfo M (Box 16)
  - Fernandez, Salvador (Box 16)
  - Fernberger, Samuel W (Box 16)
  - Ferris, Edythe (Box 16)
  - Ferris, Nellie (Box 16)
  - Ferris, Richard B (Box 16)
  - Ferron, R (Box 16)
  - Fesmire, Vincent R (Box 16)
  - Fewkes, Bernice B (Box 16)
  - Fewkes, Vladimir J (Box 16)
  - Field Museum of Natural History (Box 16)
    - Laufer, Berthold (Box 16)
    - Martin, Paul S (Box 16)
    - Simms, S C (Box 16)
    - Watson, Rose J (Box 16)
    - Wilcoxson, Emily M (Box 16)
    - [?], Eric (Box 16)
  - Field, Eugene, Society (Box 16)
    - Hartwig, John George (Box 16)
  - Field, Henry (Box 16)
  - Fillete, Edmond M A (Box 16)
  - Fina, Ramon (Box 16)
  - Finkler, Norman (Box 16)
  - Fiore, Vivian (Box 16)
  - Firestone, Mrs. Jean (Box 16)
  - Fisher, G. S (Box 16)
  - Fisher, George S (Box 16)
  - Flaccus, Louis W (Box 16)
  - Flegel, Perry S (Box 16)
  - Floyd, Mrs. Mary Play (Box 16)
  - Flye, O. L (Box 16)
  - Flynn, John E (Box 16)
  - Fogg, John M., Jr (Box 16)
  - Foley, H. F (Box 16)
  - Foley, J. P (Box 16)
  - Folkways Records & Service Corp (Box 16)
    - Asch, Moses (Box 16)
    - Lingelbach, William E (Box 16)
  - Folsom, Franklin (Box 16)
  - Foote, Helen S (Box 16)
  - Forbes, Edward W (Box 16)
  - Ford, Fred C (Box 16)
  - Fordyce, John R (Box 16)
  - Forer, Morris (Box 16)
  - Foreword to book by Muriel Fellows (Box 16)
  - Forman, Henry Chandlee (Box 16)
  - Forrest, Ann M (Box 16)
  - Foshag, W. F (Box 16)
  - Foster, Eunice (Box 16)
  - Foster, George M (Box 16)
  - Foster, George N (Box 16)
  - Foster, James W (Box 16)
  - Foster, Lawrence (Box 16)
  - Fowler, Burton P (Box 16)
    - Germantown Friends School (Box 16)
  - Fowler, Melvin L (Box 16)
    - Satterthwaite, Linton, Jr (Box 16)
  - Franchey, John (Box 16)
  - Franco Lora, Rodrigo E (Box 16)
  - Franco, E (Box 16)
  - Franco, Jose L (Box 16)
  - Franklin Institute (Box 16)
    - Allen, Henry B (Box 16)
    - Rainey, Froelich G (Box 16)
  - Franklin, Harold (Box 16)
  - Franks, Robert (Box 16)
  - Franksen, Jean (Box 16)
  - Frau, Salvador Canals (Box 16)
  - Fredericks, Lillian (Box 16)
  - Free Library of Philadelphia (Box 16)
    - Brinton, Christian (Box 16)
    - Price, F. H (Box 16)
  - Free, Jack (Box 16)
  - Freedman, Adolph (Box 16)
  - Frencey, Adolph D (Box 16)
  - French, Paul Comly (Box 16)
    - Cross, Dorothy (Box 16)
  - Friend, Neita O (Box 16)
    - Dam, Mrs. Loring (Box 16)
    - Toothaker, Charles R (Box 16)
  - Froelich, Adele (Box 16)
  - Frost, S W (Box 16)
    - Danforth, Charles H (Box 16)
  - Frost, Stuart W (Box 16)
  - Fuchs, Helmuth (Box 16)
  - Fuhrmann, Ernst (Box 16)
  - Fulton, Mrs. Merle (Box 16)
  - Fulweiler, John H (Box 16)
  - Furman, Erwin H (Box 16)
  - Furst, James C (Box 16)
  - Gabor, Robert (Box 17)
  - Gagnon, Barbara (Box 17)
  - Gaines, E F (Box 17)
  - Gall, August Freiherr V (Box 17)
  - Gallagher, Madeline (Box 17)
  - Gallatin, Albert (Box 17)
  - Gallenkamp, Charles (Box 17)
  - Galligan, Alice (Box 17)
  - Gamble, Kathryn E (Box 17)
  - Gamio, Manuel (Box 17)
    - Comas, Juan (Box 17)
  - Gamis, Everardo (Box 17)
  - Gamiz, Everardo (Box 17)
  - Gann, Thomas (Box 17)
  - Garcia Lavin, Jose Octavio (Box 17)
  - Garcia, Julia P (Box 17)
  - Gardiner, Harry G (Box 17)
  - Gardner, Emelyn E (Box 17)
  - Gardner, Paul (Box 17)
  - Garfield, Viola E (Box 17)
  - Garretson, George (Box 17)
  - Garrett, Erwin Clarkson (Box 17)
  - Garrett, Samuel J (Box 17)
  - Garrido. Tomás Garrido Co (Box 17)
  - Gary, George E (Box 17)
  - Gaskill, C S (Box 17)
    - Galentini (Box 17)
  - Gates collection (Box 17)
  - Gates' library - disposal (McComas, Mrs. Edith) (Box 17)
  - Gates, Thomas S (Box 17)
  - Gates, William (Box 17)
  - Gavica, C (Box 17)
  - Gay, Hazel (Box 17)
  - Gayoso, José A (Box 17)
  - Gayton, Anna H (Box 17)
  - Gebhard, David (Box 17)
  - Geigel, Jesse J (Box 17)
  - Gemmill, Winifred Dunlop (Box 17)
  - Genovese, M (Box 17)
  - Gentry, Howard Scott (Box 17)
  - Geoghegen, R H (Box 17)
  - Gerberich, Albert H (Box 17)
  - Gerbrands, A. A (Box 17)
    - Satterthwaite, Linton Jr (Box 17)
  - German, Horace (Box 17)
  - Gettler, George C (Box 17)
  - Ghilardi, Felix (Box 17)
  - Gibbons, Edmund (Box 17)
  - Gibbs, H. D (Box 17)
  - Giddings, J. Louis (Box 17)
  - Gideon, Henry J (Box 17)
  - Giesecke, Albert A (Box 17)
  - Giessing, Gutorm (Box 17)
  - Giffen Duyvis, Gida E G Van (Box 17)
  - Gifford, Edward W (Box 17)
  - Gilbert, O. R (Box 17)
  - Gilkyson, Phoebe H (Box 17)
  - Gill, Mabel Woodrow (Box 17)
  - Gill, Richard C (Box 17)
  - Gillet, Joseph E (Box 17)
  - Gillin, John Philip (Box 17)
  - Gilson, Betty L (Box 17)
  - Gimbi, A W (Box 17)
  - Gimpera, P Bosch (Box 17)
  - Gladwin, Harold S (Box 17)
  - Glaser, Mollie B (Box 17)
  - Gleeson, Gerald A (Box 17)
  - Glen Mills Schools (Box 17)
    - Hickman, H B (Box 17)
  - Glenn, Mrs. Dorothy Clayton (Box 17)
  - Glusker, Anita Brenner (Box 17)
  - Glutting, Clare E (Box 17)
  - Godcharles, Frederic A (Box 17)
  - Godfrey, L M (Box 17)
  - Godfrey, Mrs (Box 17)
  - Godfrey,William S (Box 17)
  - Goetze, Albrecht (Box 17)
  - Goggin, John M (Box 17)
  - Goggin, John M (Box 17)
  - Gold ornaments from Veraguas, Panama (Box 17)
  - Goldfrank, Esther S (Box 17)
  - Goldman, Irving (Box 17)
  - Goldstein, Marcus S (Box 17)
  - Golomshtok, Eugene (Box 17)
  - Goméz, Javier Rojo (Box 17)
  - Goméz, Luis Duque (Box 17)
  - González Ramírez, Manuel (Box 17)
  - Gonzalez, Jose B (Box 17)
  - Goodenough, Ward H (Box 17)
  - Goodhue,Cornelia (Box 17)
  - Goodland, Roger (Box 17)
  - Goodrich, Pierre F (Box 17)
  - Goodwin (?), Harold S (Box 17)
    - Wardle, Harriet Newell (Box 17)
  - Gordils, B A (Box 17)
  - Gordon, George B (Box 17)
  - Gordon, George G (Box 17)
  - Gordon, Maxine W (Box 17)
  - Gordon, Richard M (Box 17)
  - Gore, M. L (Box 17)
  - Gore, W. T (Box 17)
  - Goshorn, Robert M (Box 17)
  - Gottschall, Amos H (Box 17)
  - Gower, Charlotte D (Box 17)
  - Grace Log (Box 17)
    - Wallach, Philip (Box 17)
  - Graham, Violet (Box 17)
  - Grancsas, Stephen V (Box 17)
  - Granger, René (Box 17)
  - Grant, Mrs. de Forest (Box 17)
  - Grauer, Ben (Box 17)
  - Graves, Eugene L (Box 17)
  - Gray, Fred W (Box 17)
  - Gray, Mary Katherine (Box 17)
  - Graydon, Mrs. Florence (Frank) (Box 17)
  - Greany, J Malcolm (Box 18)
  - Green, Amos R (Box 18)
  - Green, G. G., Jr (Box 18)
  - Green, Jack B (Box 18)
  - Green, Otis H (Box 18)
  - Greenleaf, C H (Box 18)
  - Greenman, M J (Box 18)
  - Greenwood, Gertrude Clausen (Box 18)
  - Gregg, Clifford C (Box 18)
  - Gregory, William K (Box 18)
  - Greist, Henry W (Box 18)
  - Greystone Corporation publication: Precolumbian American Art (Box 18)
  - Greywacz, Kathryn B (Box 18)
    - Fejos, Paul (Box 18)
  - Grieser, Norman (Box 18)
  - Griessler, Mrs. Franz (Box 18)
  - Griffin, Anthony Lee (Box 18)
  - Griffin, Edward (Box 18)
  - Griffin, James B (Box 18)
  - Griffin, Norman J (Box 18)
  - Griffiths, William H (Box 18)
  - Grim, Clarence F (Box 18)
  - Grimes, Joe (Box 18)
  - Griscom, Clayton D (Box 18)
  - Grolier Society (Box 18)
    - McLoughlin, Ellen V (Box 18)
  - Gropp, Arthur E (Box 18)
  - Grosvenor, Gilbert H (Box 18)